photoshelter.com 2007-08-14

# PhotoShelter - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We at PHOTOSHELTER.COM, a product of Bitshelter, LLC, understand that our users are concerned about how personal information is collected and used. Please be assured that we take privacy very seriously and are committed to safeguarding personal information. This notice describes our Privacy Policy, which covers the personal information that we collect at PHOTOSHELTER.COM SITE (the "Site"). By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Types of Personal Information is Collected at PHOTOSHELTER.COM?**  
We collect and maintain personal information on our Site including: 

  1. Membership Registration Information. We collect the information you supply when you become a Member of the Site, including your name, address, phone, fax or e-mail address, and the password you select. This information may be edited at any time, by logging into your member page. 
  2. Preferences and Suggestions. We collect information and suggestions that you give to us, including information about your preferences. 
  3. Publicly Posted Information. We collect information you post on the Site, and which is accessible by anyone with Internet access. 
  4. Internet Protocol Address. We also collect and store the Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses of individuals that visit our site. An IP address provides general statistical information, such as browsing activity, areas of greatest interest on the site, general demographic information and other basic information that we will use for system administration. We use such information to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. This includes helping advertisers on our site design advertisements our users might like. We normally do not combine this type of information with personally identifiable information such as membership registration information. However, we will combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a visitor in order to enforce compliance with our Terms and Conditions or to protect our Site, services, Members and other users, or others. 

**Does PHOTOSHELTER.COM use Cookies?**  
Cookies are packets of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer hard drive during visits to our site. Like other companies, we use cookies for a variety of purposes. Cookies enable us to recognize your browser and save your preferences or passwords. Cookies also allow us to track statistical information that helps us to provide improved resources and services to users. Web browsers usually accept cookies automatically. However, you can change your web browser to prevent automatic acceptance of cookies or disable cookies. If your web browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of the site's features or make purchases through the website. 

**How Does PHOTOSHELTER.COM Use My Personal Information?**   
We use personal information to provide and enhance services, respond to inquiries, and provide personalized content. Our users' name, address, e-mail address and other information is stored in our database. Personal information may also be used to track user activity so that we may better understand your preferences. We may also use your personal information to contact you about promotions, products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to be contacted with this information, please send an e-mail to support@photoshelter.com. 

We also use non-personally identifying information to improve the design and content of our site. We may also use this information to analyze site usage. 

We only keep your personal information for as long as it remains relevant or as otherwise required by law. We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law or where reasonably necessary to protect our rights or a third party's rights, for example, in response to a court order, a subpoena, a request by a law enforcement agency or to respond to claims that any content violates the right of third parties. 

Although we will strive to take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never by disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Inadvertent disclosures may occur. 

**Does PHOTOSHELTER.COM Give Personal Information to Third Parties?**   
We will only share your personal information with those who provide services to the Site. Those persons do not have any right to use your personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us. We will not sell your personal information to any third party. 

**What Happens if I Disclose My Personal Information in Public Areas on the Site?**   
We have no control over and cannot protect personal information that users disclose in public areas such as a photographer's or agency profile. If you disclose your personal information in public areas, it may be collected and used by third parties, without our or your knowledge. 

**Is My Personal Information Secure if I Link to Other Web Sites?**   
The PHOTOSHELTER.COM site contains links to sites operated by third parties that are not under the control or supervision of PHOTOSHELTER.COM. Neither PHOTOSHELTER.COM nor its directors, officers, employees, shareholders, members or representatives are responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. Once you have left our site, our privacy policy no longer applies. You must read the privacy policy of the other site to see how your personal information will be handled on the third party site. 

**How Does PHOTOSHELTER.COM Protect My Personal Information?**   
All personal information is stored in our database. Access to personal information is limited to those individuals who are authorized to use such information for business and administrative purposes. 

There are some things that you can do to help protect the security of your information as well. For instance, never give out your Password, since this is what is used to access all of your account information. Also remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you finish surfing the Internet, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information. 

**Can I update or Change the Personal Information that PHOTOSHELTER.COM has Collected?**   
Members can access, review, and edit their membership registration information at any time by logging into their member page. 

**Will the PHOTOSHELTER.COM Privacy Policy Change?**   
We may change and modify the Privacy Policy at any time. All changes become effective immediately. Notice of changes may be provided to you by posting the effective date at the top of the Privacy Policy page, by email to your email address or in other ways. Your continued use of the Site after such modifications constitutes your acknowledgment of, and agreement to be bound by, the amended Privacy Policy. Please review the Privacy Policy prior to entering personal information on the site. 

We invite you to contact us with any questions or comments regarding your personal information. Please contact us if you have any questions regarding your privacy.
